练习 7-6：在动词时态变化中保持名词重音一致。这是一个压缩版
Exercise 7-6, Consistent Noun Stress in Changing Verb Tenses. This is a condensed
练习，供你练习多种动词
exercise for you to practice simple intonation with a wide range of verb
时态下的简单语调。第一次做这个练习时，先只重读名词，
tenses. When you do the exercise the first time, go through stressing only the nouns,
dogs eat bones. Practice this until you are quite comfortable with the intonation.
The pronunciation and word connections are on the right, and the full verb tenses are
on the far left. The dogs eat the bones. Two. The dogs ate the bones. Three. The
dogs are eating the bones. Four. The dogs will eat the bones. Five. The dogs that
eat the bones. Six. The dogs that have eaten the bones. Seven. The dogs that have
eaten the bones. Eight. the dogs have eaten the bones 9 the dogs had eaten the
bones 10 the dogs that have eaten the bones 11th the dogs ought to eat the bones
12 the dogs should eat the bones 13 the dogs shouldn't eat the bones 14 the dogs
should have eaten the bones 15 the dogs shouldn't have eaten the 16. The dogs
could eat the bones. 17. The dogs couldn't eat the bones. 18. The dogs could have
eaten the bones. 19. The dogs couldn't have eaten the bones. 20. The dogs might
eat the bones. 21. The dogs might have eaten the bones. 22. The dogs must eat the
bones. 23. The dogs must have eaten the bones. 24. The dogs can eat the bones. 25.
The dogs can't eat the bones.